Indiana University School of Continuing Studies records, 1971-2008 C339
Indiana University Archives
- Non-credit Program/ Lifelong Learning Course Files, 1981-2004; undated
  - Preparing for the SAT, Spring 1996 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, General, 1992-1994 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, Martinsville, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, Instructor's Vitas, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Preparing for the SAT, Malaysian Students, Spring 1992 (Box 4)
  - SAT Workshop – Warren NT001, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - SAT Workshop – Paragi NT001, 2002 (Box 4)
  - SAT Workshop - 04ST021HU, March 22, 2004 (Box 4)
  - SAT Workshop, Nashville - 04ST031HU, March 22, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Summer SAT Workshop – 04FT050HU, July 12, 2004 (Box 4)
  - SAT Workshop – 04FT061HU, September 27, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Say What You Mean… - Bailey-Huges N835, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Scandinavian Sampler – 04SL115HU, May 4, 2004 (Box 4)
  - The Not So Simple Shakers – Lawrence N938, Fall 1997 (Box 4)
  - Sherlock Holmes/ Wizard of Oz – Silver, Spring 2000 (Box 4)
  - Singing for Amateurs, Winter 1992 (Box 4)
  - Singing Vocal Technique – Smith NA013, Fall 2001/Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - Singing for Amateurs – 04SM031HU, March 22, 2004 (Box 4)
  - The Unforgettable: The Aural Scrapbook of Great Singers - 04SM222HU, April 8, 2004 (Box 4)
  - More Singing for Amateurs – 04SM041HU, May 10, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Sir Gawain in Arthurian Romance – David NA040, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Sleeping beauty: Ballet Internationale – 04SJ031HU, April 25, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Snakes Alive!, Fall 1992 (Box 4)
  - Soccer – Freitag N886, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Spanish – Baez N015, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Spanish, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Beginning Spanish – Bosch N015, Spring 2001 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for Beginners – Bosch NA014, Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for Beginners – Grimsley, Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for Beginners – 04SL011HU, February 3, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Summer Spanish for Beginners – 04SL012HU, May 4, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for Beginners – 04FL012HU, September 14, 2004 (Box 4)
  - More Spanish – Bosch NA015, Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - More Spanish, Bloomington - 04SL021HU, March 23, 2004 (Box 4)
  - More Spanish – 04FL021HU, October 16, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for the Workplace – Grimsley NA026, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - Spanish for the Workplace - Grimsley NA026, Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - Spindle and the Shrine – Calinescu N707, Fall 2000 (Box 4)
  - Thrills and Agonies: The History of Sports – English, Spring 2001 (Box 4)
  - Spring Birding in Indiana – Hengeveld N201, undated (Box 4)
  - A Story is a Building: How to Envision, and Revise the Short Story – Gossy, Spring 2004 (Box 4)
  - Strength and Power Training for the Young Athlete and Coach – Eksten N807, Winter 1992 (Box 4)
  - Symbols of Power, Emblems of Faith: Russia's Art and Architect – Kennedy N894, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Taking Charge of Your Health – Harter N998, Fall 2000 (Box 4)
  - Tour of the T.C. Steele Exhibit – Foster N854, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Team Building – N821, Fall 1991 (Box 4)
  - Telling the Truth: How to Turn Real Life into Story – Gossy N567, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Beginning Tennis, Spring 1992 (Box 4)
  - Therapeutic Drugs and Their Interactions – Beck N765, Spring 1990 (Box 4)
  - Town-Gown Course, Collins Living Learning Center, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Turf Worth Talking About – N840, March 1997 (Box 4)
  - Vegetarian Cooking, undated (Box 4)
  - Homage to Verdi – Jacobi NA027, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - Victorian Entertainments – Gray N791, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Visual Exploration: Learning to Read the Language of Art, April 1, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Walking for Fitness – Laczkowski N718, Spring 1992 (Box 4)
  - Power Walking for Fitness – 04SS161HU, April 3, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Walking Tour of Campus Trees and the Arboretum – N754, Fall 1993 (Box 4)
  - Weather, Spring 1994 (Box 4)
  - Weight Management – 04SS041HU, April 8, 2004 (Box 4)
  - The Legacy of Herman B. Wells: Living with Art – Foster NA008, Fall 2001 (Box 4)
  - Lucky Being: Herman B. Wells in Historical Context – Capshew N972, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Joyce Williams Courses, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Women in Greek Art and Society – Marer-Banasik N874, Spring 1994 (Box 4)
  - William Wordsworth and the Age of English Romanticism, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Wordsworth and Romanticism – Johnston, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Writing for Awareness: The Art of Personal Journaling – 04SH061HU, April 8, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Writing for Children – Harik N910, Spring 1996 (Box 4)
  - Writing the Picture Book – 04FH031HU, November 3, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Writing Retreat at Mary Anderson Center for the Arts – N568, 2000 (Box 4)
  - History of Wylie House – Burgess N923, 2000 (Box 4)
- Lifelong Learning Day Trips, 1982-2002
  - A Visit to IU's Bradford Woods, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Chicago, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Theatre Circle Trip to Steppenwolf Theatre in Chicago, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Trip to the Cincinnati Zoo and Museum Center, Fall 1993 (Box 4)
  - Cincinnati Trip, Fall 1995 (Box 4)
  - Rocks and Flowers of Clifty Falls State Park, Leader- Professor Gary Lane, May 1991 (Box 4)
  - Columbus, Indiana: The Architectural Showplace of America, Fall 1990 (Box 4)
  - Columbus, Indiana: The Architectural Showplace of America, Fall 1997 (Box 4)
  - Corydon- General Information (Box 5)
  - Corydon, Indiana- Donald an Edith Carmony, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour- Corydon, October 1986 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour- Corydon, April 1987 (Box 5)
  - Tour to Cedar Farm and Corydon, Fall 1992 (Box 5)
  - Tour of Corydon and Cedar Farm- Don Carmony for Meadowood, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Evaluations: Carmony Tours, Spring 1985 (Box 5)
  - Field Trips by Gary Lane, 1985-1992 (Box 5)
  - Fort Wayne Educational Tour- Carmony, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Fort Wayne: Lincoln and Limberlost, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Waldron Shale in Southeastern Indiana- Hope and Vernon, Indiana, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Connor Prairie, Indianapolis, Spring 1988 (Box 5)
  - Educational Tour to IUPUI and Conner Prairie, May 1989 (Box 5)
  - Tour to the Eiteljorg Museum and State Capitol Building, Indianapolis, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Trip to the Indianapolis Zoo, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to Indianapolis, Spring 1992 (Box 5)
  - Visit to the Children's Museum, Indianapolis, Spring 1993 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to Indianapolis, Fall 1994 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to the IRT, Pygmalion, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Indianapolis: One Hundred Years, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to the IRT, Spring 1996 (Box 5)
  - Indianapolis Museum Duo: Eiteljorg and the Indianapolis Museum of Art, Fall 1997 (Box 5)
  - Theater Trip (To Kill A Mockingbird), Fall 1997 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to IRT, The Three Sisters Rosensweig, Spring 1997 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to the IRT, "Abe Lincoln in Illinois", 1998 (Box 5)
  - "A Backward Look": The Sesquicentennial James Whitcomb Riley Tour, 1999 (Box 5)
  - A Day in Prairietown: Conner Prairie, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Discovering Indianapolis's White River State Park, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Amadeus: Theatre Trip to the IRT, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Gift to the Tsars: Indianapolis Art Museum Trip, Fall 2001 (Box 5)
  - Ah, Wilderness: Theatre Trip to the IRT, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Copenhagen: Trip to the IRT, 2002 (Box 5)
  - New Indiana State Museum, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Kentucky Trip, Includes Shakertown- Donald and Edith Carmony, October 1983 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour- Shakertown, Lexington, KY, May 1987 (Box 5)
  - Lexington, Kentucky- Educational Tour by the Carmonys, April 1986 (Box 5)
  - Limestone, Fall 1992 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour New Albany/Louisville, April 1985 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to Louisville, Fall 1991 (Box 5)
  - Theatre Trip to Louisville, Fall 1992 (Box 5)
  - Thornton Wilder Plays: Actors Theatre Louisville, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Macbeth: Theatre Trip to Actors Theatre, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Jitney: Actors Theatre Louisville, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Madison, Indiana General Information, 1988-1994 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tours to Madison Indiana and the "Upriver" Communities, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Madison, Indiana Trip led by Don Carmony for Meadowood, May 4, 1993 (Box 5)
  - "Madison in Bloom," Madison, Indiana, April 1995 (Box 5)
  - Missouri Botanical Gardens, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Geology of Monroe County, Gary Lane Field Trip, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour, New Harmony, April 1983 (Box 5)
  - Carmony Tour, New Harmony, June 1988 (Box 5)
  - New Harmony, Indiana, one day trip, October 1991 (Box 5)
  - Falls of the Ohio- Gary Lane Trips, Fall 1995 (Box 5)
  - Orange County Fieldtrip: Karst and Virgin Forest, Fall 2001 (Box 5)
  - Rocks and Flowers, Versailles State Park, Spring 1992 (Box 5)
  - A Walk in the Forest, Spring 2002 (Box 5)
  - Plain and Fancy: A Trip to Montgomery, West Baden and French Lick, Indiana, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Trip to West Baden Springs Hotel and French Lick Resort Hotel, 1999 (Box 5)
    (19 photographs removed and transferred to the photography collection)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1996 (Box 5)
- Student Files, 1995-2004 (Box 6)
  Conditions Governing Access
  (Series is CLOSED to researchers at this time.)
  - Student Profiles/ GPAs (Box 6)
    - Fall 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Spring 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Fall 1996-1997 (Box 6)
    - Spring 1996-1997 (Box 6)
    - Fall 1997-1998 (Box 6)
    - Spring 1997-1998 (Box 6)
    - Fall 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Spring 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 7)
    - Spring 2000-2001 (Box 7)
  - Student Statistics (Box 7)
    - Spring 1995, Fall 2000-2001 (Box 7)
    - Fall 2000-2001 (Box 7)
    - Fall 2001-2002 (Box 7)
    - Fall 2003-2004 (Box 7)